Hello, Mr. Turtle! Hi, Mr. Turtle!
《・～（唯）もしもしかめよ～
かめさんよ～》
《・～せかいのうちで　おまえほど》
Nothing in the world moves as slow as you.
《・～あゆみののろい　ものはない》
《・～どうして
そんなにのろいのか》
Why are you so slow?
《（和）唯ちゃーん》
Yui-chan?
Come on!
《（和）もう　早く》
《あッ　和ちゃん》
Oh, Nodoka-chan.
《ほらッ　散歩行っちゃうよ》
Look, it's time for our stroll.
《あッ　待って～》
Wait!
う～ん
うーん
何　うなってるのよ　唯
What's troubling you, Yui?
あッ　和ちゃん　志望校
どこにしようか迷ってて
Nodoka-chan!
I was just wondering which college I'd like to attend...
What?!
えッ　進路調査表
まだ出してなかったの？
You still haven't turned in your senior questionnaire?!
みんな　とっくに提出してるわよ
でも　でも私　頭よくないし
You know, everyone turned theirs in ages ago!
But, but... I'm not smart and I
don't know much about college.
大学のことも　よくわかんないし
唯…　このままじゃ本当に
ニートになっちゃうよ
Yui...
At that rate, you're really going to become a NEET.
あッ　今回は重たいよ　その言葉
I can feel the weight of your words this time!
Shoot! We can't stop! We won't stop!
Singing out loud all day long!
We'll all take the chance to
jump up and make a wish,
and shout out
about our fun lives!
If we mess up, let's pretend it's a rehearsal and redo it!
Everyone has their own little cosmos which we call "heart."
It's tightly packed with emotions and love.
We're busy getting excited, blue, or in-between.
It's chaos every day, so might as well make a song out of it!
And sing all about it!
We unconsciously study music even in class.
We can start making rhythms with air guitars!
It's the feeling that counts!
Imagining the beats, we'll enjoy ourselves freely!
You lose if you can't have fun!
Sorry! We can't let go! We won't let that go!
Swinging around in every possible way like crazy girls,
we'll hit whatever note we want to!
Maybe groove a little like that, and reverb like so.
We want to try everything, until we die.
We'll chase tomorrow together,
dream a little when we take a break.
Let's be bold and faithful and shake this stage up a bit!
Once you feel the ovation, you can't get enough of it!
Visit www.coalguys.com for hi-speed DDLs!
The Future!
うーん　うーん…
Well... I guess I'll be a NEET then.
もう　ニートでいいや
ニ～ト
やめなさいって
N-E-E-T.
Stop it.
結局　和ちゃんは第一志望
どこにしたの？
So what did you end up choosing, Nodoka-chan?
私？　私は国立の方にしたわ
ちょっと無謀な気もするけど
Me?
I thought I'd try a national university.
I may be getting way over my head, but I figured it'd be worth a shot.
頑張って目指してみようかなって
Then I'll do that too.
じゃあ　私もそこにする
軽ッ
What?
だって　和ちゃんと
一緒がいいんだもん
But I want to be with you, Nodoka-chan!
はあ…
（律）な～に　騒いでんの？
練習行くぞ
What's the ruckus?
Let's go to practice.
いや…　唯がね
Well, you see...
（澪）唯　まだ進路
決めてなかったのか？
Yui, you didn't decide on a plan yet?
澪ちゃんはどこにしたの？
第一志望
What did you put as your first choice, Mio-chan?
私は推薦もらおうかなと
I figured... I'd get a recommendation.
「推薦」っと
Recommendation.
唯　「推薦」って何か知ってる？
さあ？
Yui, do you even know what that is?
No.
ムギちゃんはどこに？
Mugi-chan, what about you?
（紬）私は前　話した女子大に
My first choice is the all-girls college I told you about.
すごい　名門だな
Wow, that's a really prestigious school.
私もそこに
いい加減にしなさい
Then I'll go there too.
That's enough.
ムギちゃんのとこって
難しいの？
Mugi-chan, is it... hard to get in?
えっと　ちょうど赤本持ってるから
見てみる？
Well...
I have the Barron's guide with me... Would you like to take a look?
どれどれ　うわッ　英語！
Let's see.
English?!
目がチッカチッカする
My eyes hurt...
現実を知ったな
Welcome to reality.
ここは日本だ！
英語なんて必要ない
This is Japan!
We don't need filthy English!
必要なーい！
Screw it!
我々は　日本語だけで生きていく！
生きていくー！
We will live on with just our sacred Japanese language!
Live on!
ワハハハハハッ
（澪）学校の英語で赤点とってると
留年だぞ
If you fail English at school, you won't be able to graduate.
ガビーン
Oh, crap!
でも　入試だったら　ほかの教科で
いい点とればいいの
As long as you do fine on other subjects, the entrance exam won't be a problem.
ほらッ　国語もあるのよ
Look, there's Japanese literature.
Cool!
そっか
Classical literature?
古文！　よしッ
りっちゃんにパス
Catch, Ricchan!
おう　よーし
Right!
なになに？　次の助動詞が同じ
使われ方のものを選びなさい
Let's take a look.
From the following, pick the auxiliary verbs that are used in the same manner.
ふんふんふん
こんなの習ってなーいッ
I've never seen this type of question before!
それ　１年の範囲だぞ
えッ？
That's freshmen stuff.
そんな…
No...
〈バカなッ〉
Impossible!
（紬）助動詞はね　歌で覚えるって
習わなかった？
Don't you remember the songs to memorize auxiliary verbs?
・～む　ず　む　ず　じ　し　む
まし　まほし～
Mu zu mu zu ji shi mu mashi mahoshi~
I really want itchy rashes
Ru ra ra ru sasu ri ri ri~
Slowly, slowly, on the field
・～る　ら　ら　る　さーす
りー　りー　りー
・～つ　ぬ　たり　け　り　たし
Tsu nu tari ke ri tashi ta shi ki kemu~
Kick, fall, it's dangerous
・～た　し　き　けむ～
・～らむ　べし　らし　まじ
Ramu beshi rashi maji nari meri~
The lamb Betty is so focused
・～なーり　めりー
・～どうしてそんなり
たり　ごとし～
Doushitesonnari tari gotoshi~
Why is it so noisy?
だよね？
ちゃんと覚えてるじゃないか
Right?
See, you do know the song!
で　これをどうすればいいの？
だあッ
So what do I do with it?
（澪）それじゃ　意味ないッ
What's the point in knowing the song?!
りっちゃんは　どこにしたの？
Ricchan, what's your first choice?
私は「未定」って書いた　進路なんて
まだ全然わからないしな
I put down "undecided."
I have absolutely no clue about my future goals and whatnot.
おーッ　じゃあ　私も未定にする
・（澪）いいのか　それで？
Then I'll put down "undecided" as well.
紙切れなんかに　私たちの未来は
決められないぜー
Are you sure about that?
A sheet of paper's not gonna make our futures!
ないぜー
That's right!
３年２組の田井中さん　平沢さん
至急　職員室に来なさい
Tainaka-san and Hirasawa-san from class 3-2, please come to the staff room immediately.
ガビーン
Oh, crap!
Of course it won't work.
（澪）いいわけないか…
Guys, go ahead and practice without us.
先に部室に行っててください
面倒くせー
What a pain...
まったく…
Goodness.
・（澪）大変だな　和
It must be a lot of work, Nodoka.
澪もね　お互いさま
Right back at you.
唯は　小さい頃から
全然　変わらないのよね
Yui hasn't changed a bit since she was little.
あれでもマシにはなったんだけど
It might be hard to believe,
but she's improved a lot.
Ritsu could be great if she took things more seriously.
律もまじめにやれば
できる子なんだけどな
（和）唯も集中力はすごいんだけど
The same can be said about Yui,
though her concentration is amazing.
その話の続き　部室でしない？
Can we continue this conversation in the music room?
なんで　ムギがそんなに
張り切ってるんだ？
Why are you so excited, Mugi?
（梓）あッ　お疲れさまです
Good afternoon.
（澪・紬）お疲れさま
おじゃまします
Excuse me.
That announcement was for Yui-
senpai and Ritsu-senpai, right?
さっきの放送　唯先輩たちですよね
（澪）ああ　まッ　自業自得だけどな
Yeah, they dug their own graves.
（梓）また　何か
やっちゃったんですか？
Did they screw up something again?
また？
あ…　ちょっとね
Again?
Oh, it's nothing big.
進路のことで
相談があるみたいなの
They were called in to discuss their future plans and stuff.
ふーん
はい　どうぞ　和ちゃん
ありがとう
Here you go, Nodoka-chan.
Thanks.
（澪）そういや　和は　いつ
唯と知り合ったんだ？
Speaking of which, when did you meet Yui?
幼稚園のときよ
どんな出会いだったのかしら？
When we were in kindergarten.
How did you meet?
うーん　特別なきっかけは
なかったんだけど…
It wasn't really anything special...
《一緒に描こう》
《（和）うん　いいよ》
Let's draw.
Okay.
・（和）何か　知らない間に
横にいたわね
Before I realized it, she was right next to me.
・（澪）本能的に　頼れる人だと
感じたのだろうか？
Maybe her instincts told her
that you're a reliable person.
《唯ちゃん　もうできたの？》
Yui-chan, are you done already?
《おいしそう》
《そうだね》
It looks tasty.
Yeah.
《あ～》
《なめちゃ　ダメ》
Don't put it in your mouth!
最初から　そんなだったのか
She hasn't changed at all.
そう　そのときからしょっちゅう
同じクラスになってるの
Yeah.
And we've been in the same class almost every year since then.
不思議な縁なのは
間違いないわね
We have mysterious bonds connecting us.
Did she give you a lot of trouble?
（梓）やっぱり　いろいろ
困ったりしました？
えッ　うーん　困ったって言えば
困ったのかな→
Trouble? I guess you could say that.
小学校のとき
キャンプに行ったんだけど…
We went camping in grade school.
《レトルトって聞いてなかった？》
Don't you remember we're supposed to bring pre-cooked food?
・（梓）唯先輩らしいですね
Sounds like Yui-senpai.
・（和）そういえば　家庭科で
たこ焼き作ったときもね→
That reminds me of when we were
making octopus balls in cooking class.
みんなで　材料を持ち寄ることに
なったんだけど
We were assigned to bring different ingredients, but...
《唯　たこ出して？》
《えッ》
Yui, pass me the octopus.
・（和）たこ担当の唯が
たこ持ってくるの忘れたの→
Yui was in charge of the octopus, but she forgot to bring it.
結局　たこなし焼きを
作ったんだけどね
In the end, we just made grilled balls.
《あッ　たこなしでもおいしいね》
These taste pretty good even without octopus!
たこなし焼き　クククッ
Grilled balls...
ほかにも　語り尽くせないほど
やらかしてくれたわね
These stories are just a dime a dozen.
でも　あの悪気のない笑顔を見ると
なぜか許しちゃうのよね
But when I see her smiling so innocently, I always end up forgiving her.
わかるわ～
そんなもんですかね
I know that feeling.
Is that the case?
そうそう　さっき唯がこれでも
マシになったって言ったけど
Oh, right...
I mentioned earlier that Yui's gotten a lot better lately.
それって多分　軽音部のおかげだと
思うの　だから　ありがとう
I think it's all because of you guys.
As her friend, I thank you all very much.
和ちゃんは大人ね
ホント　何かママみたい
Nodoka-chan, you're so mature.
Yeah, it's like you're a mommy.
（紬・梓）ママ？
Mommy?
おっ　お母さん
I mean, mom!
・（さわ子）自分の将来なんだから
ちゃんと考えなさい
It's your own future, so take the time to think about it.
へーい
唯ちゃんはまだ決められないの？
Yeah, sure...
Yui-chan, you still can't make up your mind?
何だか　ずっと先のことだから
想像できなくて
Well, it's hard to think about something that won't happen for a while.
It'll be here before you realize it.
ずっと先じゃないでしょ
あっという間よ
Time flies, after all.
No wonder you're beginning to look old.
さわちゃんも　年をとるわけだ
何だって？
Say that again.
そういや　さわちゃんは高校時代
あんなだったのに
Wait, you were like this back in high school.
なんで　先生になろうと思ったの？
So why did you want to become a teacher all of a sudden?
えッ　いや…　それは…
Well, that's...
えーッ　何　何？
あの…　恥ずかしいから
Wait, what happened?
It's really embarrassing.
参考にしたいので
ぜひ聞かせてください
Tell us! It might help us make our decision!
実はね　そのとき好きだった人が
先生になりたいって言うから…
Well... the person I liked back then said he wanted to become a teacher,
じゃあ　私もーって
不純だな
so I was like "me too!"
That's ignoble.
それで　その人とはどうなったの？
ふられたわよ　うわーん
So what happened with him?
He rejected me.
でもさ　その人のおかげで　大学に
行けて　先生になれてるんだよね
But because of him, you got a teaching degree and became a teacher, right?
そうだよ　大切なのは過去じゃなく
今だよ　さわちゃん
That's right.
The present, not the past, is what matters.
でも　その今も
彼氏はいないんだっけ？
But you still don't have a boyfriend.
うわーん
おッ　唯　どうだった？
Yui, how was it?
さわちゃんの過去がまた一つ
明らかになった
We've solved the mystery of another piece of Sawa-chan's history.
えッ　怒られたんじゃないのか
You weren't scolded or something?
いや～　何だか人生いろいろだねえ
You never know what's going to happen in life.
また　何かしでかしたんじゃ
ないだろうな
This sounds fishy... What did you do now?
違う　違う　いろんなことがあって
人は強くなっていくってことだよ
Honestly, nothing.
I'm just saying people grow stronger upon encountering different things.
うん？
進路調査表は　あれでよかったの？
ダメだった
So she accepted your questionnaires?
Nope.
将来なりたいものとか　ないの？
What do you want to be later on in life?
なりたいものか…
What I want to be, huh...
澪ちゃん　何がいいと思う？
自分で決めろ
Mio-chan, what do you think I'll be good at?
Figure it out yourself.
う～
Back when we were in grade school, didn't you say you wanted to teach kindergarten?
小学校のときは　幼稚園の先生って
言ってなかった？
そうだった
That's right!
たしか「将来の夢」って題で
作文を発表したときに…
I remember when we were reading out our essays about our future...
《私の将来の夢は
幼稚園の先生です》
My dream is to become a kindergarten teacher.
When I become one, I will play with little children forever and ever.
《幼稚園の先生になって》
《子どもたちとずっと
遊んでいたいです》
唯らしいな
That's so like you.
作文の発表って言えば　澪が
優秀賞をとったときがあってさ…
Oh, speaking of essays...
Mio won an award once.
うわーッ　それを言うな
Don't bring that up!
聞きたい！
聞きた～い
I want to hear it.
Me too.
あ　梓　練習しよう　練…
うおッ
Azusa, let's practice!
Le-
観念するしかないな　澪
I suggest you give up, Mio.
When we were in grade school, Mio was quiet and meek.
小学校の頃の澪は　もの静かで
おとなしい子だったなあ
I remember she was always reading a book.
ずっと本ばっか読んでた気がする
そんでもって…
And then...
What are you reading?!
《（律）何読んでるの？》
《（澪）ひッ》
今にも増して
恥ずかしがり屋だったんだ
She was even shyer than she is now.
Hey, show me! Show me!
《ねえ　見せて　見せて》
その反応がおもしろくて
I loved triggering her reactions.
《澪ちゃんって　絵もうまいんだ？》
Mio-chan, you're an amazing artist!
I bugged her all the time.
しょっちゅう　ちょっかい
出してたっけ
Wow, a perfect score!
《すごい　１００点だ！》
Wow...
いいな　私も
ちょっかい出したかった
I wish I was there to do that.
Isn't that bullying?
それって　いじめじゃないんですか
違う　違う
Not at all.
小学生のときって　好きな子に
ちょっかい出したくなるじゃん
You know how kids like to tease the people they like?
あれだよ　あれ
It was kinda like that.
But we weren't all that close at first, were we?
でも最初の頃は　特別　仲よしって
わけじゃなかったよな？
Of course we weren't!
そりゃそうだろッ
あんなことされたら
Do you remember what you did to me?
思い出したら　イライラしてきた
おでこ出しなさい
I'm getting irritated by just thinking about it.
Hand over your forehead.
えッ　何すんの？
What are you going to do?
Sign: Eye
あッ
My forehead...
私のおでこ…
水性だから安心しろ
Don't worry, it's water-based.
So, what happened with the essay reading?
それで　作文の発表は
どうだったの？
I thought I changed the topic.
お　覚えてた？
いいじゃん　澪　話してあげなよ
Oh, come on, Mio.
Just tell us about it.
うう…
I'm a triclops!
三つ目星人だじょー
キャー
When I was in fourth grade, I was awarded the prefecture prize for my essay.
小４の頃だっけ　私の作文
県から賞をもらって
People who received the award had to read their essay out loud in front of everyone at the school assembly.
・（澪）賞をもらった人は
全校集会でみんなの前で→
読まなきゃいけなくてさ→
読みたくなくて　落ち込んでた私に
I didn't want to do it, and I was feeling down, but then...
《どうしたの？》
What's wrong?
Ritsu talked to me and comforted me.
・（澪）律が
話しかけてくれたんだっけ
You don't want to read your essay?
《え　作文読みたくない　なんで？》
《だって恥ずかしいもん》
Why not?
Well, it's embarrassing.
《恥ずかしくないよ　すごいよ》
《ぜ　全然すごくなんかないよ》
It's not embarrassing at all!
You're amazing!
I-I'm not amazing at all.
《だって　賞をもらったの
クラスで澪ちゃんだけだよ》
But you're the only person in our class who won the award.
《私だったら　みんなに自慢するな》
If it were me, I'd be bragging about it.
《だったら　りっちゃんが
賞もらえばよかったのにッ》
Then you should have gotten the award!
I don't want to read it out loud in front of everyone!
《みんなの前で読むのヤだよ！》
I-I'm sorry...
《ご　ごめんなさい》
I didn't know... that Mio-chan could be so loud.
《澪ちゃんって　こんな大きな声
出せるんだ》
She's... interesting!
《何か…　おもしろい》
Hey, come over to my house right now.
《ねえ　今からうちにおいでよ
特訓しよう》
I'll train you well!
《えッ　あッ　で　でも…》
B-But...
《いいから　いいから》
Oh, just come on.
《それでは　４年１組　出席番号
１番　秋山澪さん　どうぞ》
Now, let's welcome Akiyama Mio-san from class 4-1.
I can't do it...
《できないよ》
《えッ　台　低かったかな》
Is the box too low?
《もっと高くする？》
《そ　そういうことじゃなくて》
Want me to raise it?
Th-That's not the problem.
《あッ　ちょっと待って》
Give me a minute.
Let me take this off...
《これをこうやって…》
《えっと　こうして　こう…》
Like this...
《はい　でき上がり！》
Okay, I'm done.
《なーに　それ？》
《パイナップル》
What's that?
A pineapple!
《お父さんがね　緊張したときは
観客をジャガイモだと思えって》
My dad told me that when I'm nervous, I should just treat the crowd as a bunch of potatoes.
But I can't be a potato, so I'm a pineapple!
《でも私　ジャガイモのまねは
できないから》
《パイナップル
パイナップルのまね～》
《全然　似てないよ》
You don't look like one at all.
...and that is how it is passed down from one person to another.
《（澪）ということで　人から
人へ伝わっていくのでした→》
The end.
《終わり　４年１組　秋山澪》
Akiyama Mio, class 4-1.
・（澪）律のおかげで　すごく
リラックスできたんだよな
Thanks to Ritsu, I was able to relax.
いい話ね
That's a great story.
昔はいい子だったんですね
律先輩
You used to be such a good girl, Ritsu-senpai.
That's totally not like her at all.
やっぱり　りっちゃんの
キャラじゃないよ
Don't you know how to give complements?!
素直にほめるってことを
知らないのかい？
So, did the essay presentation go well?
あ　それで　作文発表は
うまくいったんですか？
Well, Mio wrote the essay, and the
content was like that of a fairy-tale...
まあ　澪が書いた作文だから
内容がとてもメルヘンで…
Itchy! Itchy! Itchy! Itchy! Itchy!
そこは察してくれ
Please imagine the rest.
でもあれからだよな　よく律の家に
遊びにいくようになったのは
But ever since then, I started
frequently going over to your house.
Yeah!
そうそう　私がいろいろ
教えてあげたっけか
I taught you a lot of things.
Yeah, a lot...
そう　いろいろ
If you don't want to be shy, you must first have confidence in yourself.
《恥ずかしがり屋を直すには
自分に自信を持たせなきゃ》
《まずはしゃべり方
語尾に「だぜ」をつければ》
First, let's fix how you talk.
If you end your sentences with "you know," you'll sound very confident.
《自信満々に見えるよ》
I-I'm Akiyama Mio, you know?
《わ　私は　秋山澪だぜ》
《そうそう　その調子》
That's right, just like that!
いろいろ…
A lot of things...
ろくなこと教えてもらってない
気がしてきた
I don't think I learned anything decent from you.
Maybe I shouldn't have asked for your help.
やっぱり　律に
助けてもらうんじゃなかったかな
Th-That's mean, Mio-chan!
ひ　ひどいよ　澪ちゃん
It's not like you were being reserved.
唯も好き勝手　言ってたくせに
But I do thank you for intro-
ducing me to music... I guess.
でも　私に音楽を勧めてくれた
ことには　感謝してる…　かも
みおしゃん
Mio-senpai!
Mio-chan!
Wait, how did we start talking about this?
・（澪）て　私と律の話じゃなくて→
We need to figure out your future goals or careers.
今は　２人の進路調査を
どうするかだろ
Oh...
That's right.
あッ
そうだったわ
To start off, don't think too hard and just come up with something you'd like to be.
とりあえず難しく考えないで
漠然と　自分のなりたいものから
考えればいいんじゃない？
そっか　じゃあ　お花屋さんとか
I see.
What about a florist?
That sounds pretty good.
それ　いいんじゃないですか
I'm Hirasawa Yui, the town's florist.
《私　平沢唯　町のお花屋さん》
《このお花　育てるの大変かしら》
《わかりません》
Is this breed of flowers difficult to maintain?
I don't know.
Sign: Bankrupt
You'd need to know a lot about plants.
植物の知識が必要ですね
それじゃあ　会社勤めのＯＬは？
う～ん
What about a corporate worker?
《私　新米ＯＬ
今日も遅刻しちゃった　テヘッ》
I'm the new worker.
And oops, I'm late again today.
Sorry I'm late!
《すいません　遅刻しましたッ》
Your company... is next door.
《あなたの会社　隣のドアだよ》
《し　失礼しました～》
I'm so sorry!
You might have a hard time being punctual.
時間が決まってるのは無理かも
あずにゃん　しどい
Azu-nyan, you're so brutal.
バスガイドなんか　いいかもね
How about a tour guide?
Yeah!
おーッ　タダでいろんなとこ
行けるしね
I'd be able to go on free trips!
そうですね
That's true...
I'm your tour guide.
《私　バスガイド》
If you would look to your right...
《えー　皆様　右手をご覧ください
右手に　うぷッ》
To your righ...
《ございますのが　うぷッ》
That won't work since you get carsick easily.
（梓）酔いやすい人は
無理だと思います
ウエイトレスとか
Then how about a waitress?
I'm a waitress!
《私　ウエイトレス》
いっぱい注文
覚えなきゃだぞ
You'd have to memorize a lot of orders.
Then how about a pâtissiere?
菓子職人とか？
I'm a pâtissiere!
《私　お菓子屋さん》
She's going to eat all the desserts.
自分で
食べちゃいそう
That's very possible.
Well... just put down the thing that you'd like to do most.
まあ　今は自分たちが
思いつくものでいいんじゃない？
Something I like to do most...
自分で思いつくもの…
そっか　りっちゃん
おうッ！
I know!
Ricchan!
Yeah!
却下！
Sign: Musician
No.
あれー？
Huh?
Why did we get turned down?
なんでだよ
ちゃんと書いたのにねえ
We gave a lot of thought about it...
ダメでした　隊長！
It was a failure, Captain!
ミュージシャンって…
まじめにやりなさいッ
A musician?
Stop goofing around!
まじめ…　なんだけど
But... we're not.
Nodoka-chan's laughing!
和ちゃんが　笑ってる
あきれてるんじゃ？
I think she's lost all hopes for you.
実は　和ちゃんに
笑ってもらうように仕込んだ
You see, it was actually a well-crafted joke aimed at Nodoka-chan.
体を張ったギャグだったのです
No, she probably thinks pigs will fly before you become a musician.
いや　無理がありますよ　唯さん
憂は　卒業したらどうするの？
Ui, what are you going to do once you graduate?
I can't tell her.
I can't tell her I want to go to where she's going because I'm worried about her...
〈（憂）言えない　お姉ちゃんが
心配で〉
〈お姉ちゃんと同じところに
行きたいなんて〉
わ　私は　まだ考えてないよ
I-I haven't given thought about it.
そっか　ちゃんと考えなきゃ
ダメだよ
I see.
Make sure you do.
お姉ちゃんは？
今　考えてるところ
What about you?
I'm thinking about it right now.
〈えーッ　まだだったんだ〉
You still haven't thought it out?
I chose a school that specializes in cosmetics because I want to be a cosmetician.
私は美容師になりたいから
美容師の専門学校にした
そっか
I see.
An arts college.
芸大かな　写真の勉強するの
写真の学科ってあるの
I want to study photography.
They have courses for photography?
I'm going to go to the Tokyo University of
Foreign Studies and study abroad in China.
外語大に行って
中国に留学するんだ
へえ
I'm going to a nursery school.
私は　看護学校だよ
I'm going to help my family's liquor business.
うちの酒屋さんを手伝うの
う～ん
This is confusing me even more.
ますます　わからなくなってきたよ
Sign: For now // I will do // the best I can
よろしくお願いしますッ
Please take this!
No.
却下
えーッ
あらッ
Oh?
Excuse me...
失礼しましたー
はあ…
Deep, deep inside my heart,
there was a sanctuary where nothing ever resounded.
But now it's burning with heat, so I've forever changed.
I send out shockwaves to the world, as storms,
and tsunamis invite each other with the sound of rock and roll
to walk beside each other everywhere they go.
Whoops, I dropped my pick,
and I broke my drumstick, but hey it's all right.
I'm still a part of the usual sound,
which is actually quite miraculous!
We'll sing out loud to our hearts' content.
No matter how faint the song,
it's the one and only in the world.
We want to live our lives to the fullest
so that we won't care if we die today.
Let's play our passion to the world.
After all, this is our precious heartbeat.
We'll sing our treasured heartbeat.
So please listen!!
Preview
What's wrong, Sawa-chan?
I'm short on sweets and tea!
Why don't we have tea parties anymore?
That's a good imitation!
I'm going to lose myself...
Yui-chan?
Grandma!
Thank you!
I'm sorry for always- Ow.
My, what are you doing?
Finals!